http://www.northlandcollege.edu/legal/disclaimer/

Transcript Request
Take The Next Step.
Get Connected.
Privacy Statement
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Standards Compliance
Information found on this web site can be made available in alternative formats, such as large print, Braille, or on tape, by calling:
East Grand Forks campus: 1-800-959-6282 or TTY 800-627-3529
Thief River Falls campus: 1-800-959-6282 or TTY 800-627-3529
Note: this site has undergone major renovation and as such not all pages may be in 100% compliance. The Northland web development team is working hard to ensure compliancy. If you find a page that is not compliant or is unreadable in your browser, please contact the Marketing & Communications department immediately.
This site aims to adhere to the guidelines published by W3C and Section 508.
Northland Community & Technical College (NCTC) is an Affirmative Action/Equal Opportunity Educator and Employer. Lack of English skills will not be a barrier to admissions and participation. These documents are not to be regarded as a contract.
Future Students
Current Students
Online Students
Northland Home
Business & Industry
Employees
Alumni & Friends
Northland EAST GRAND FORKS
© 2020 Northland Community and Technical College. An affirmative action, equal opportunity employer and educator. Privacy Statement.
Lack of English skills will not be a barrier to admissions and participation.
